Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is chocolate chip cookie dough. Let
me show you how to make it. We're just
using my classic vanilla base, which is
a vanilla protein shake, vanilla bean
paste, sweetener, salt, sample gum, and
you can just blend that all together.
Throw it in the freezer for at least 16
hours. And once it's nice and frozen,
you can take it out, run under hot water
for about a minute, and then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. Now, this is the absolute key
for the recipe. this cookie dough from
Fuel Snacks. It's brand new, tastes
amazing, and it packs 15 grams of
protein per pouch. So, I threw about
half a package on top of the creamy, and
then mix it in by hand so it doesn't get
super broken up. So, that adds another 8
g of protein. And, you know, I was
looking for an alternative to the Ben &
Jerry's cookie dough bites. They're just
kind of hard to find, kind of expensive,
and these just happened to come up on my
feed and make the perfect substitution.